Payback is a beast.
Death of a Unicorn is a horror, fantasy, comedy film directed by Alex Scharfman.
A father and daughter accidentally hit and kill a unicorn while en route to a weekend retreat, where
his billionaire boss seeks to exploit the creature’s miraculous curative properties.
Elliot, played by Paul Rudd.
Ridley, played by Jenna Ortega.
Shepard, played by Will Poulter.
Odell, played by Richard E. Grant.
Belinda, played by Téa Leoni.
Dr. Bhatia, played by Sunita Mani.
Death of a Unicorn is a 2025 American dark fantasy comedy horror film
written and directed by Alex Scharfman in his directorial debut.
The films stars Paul Rudd and Jenna Ortega as well as
supporting cast Will Poulter, Téa Leoni, and Richard E.
In the film, a father and daughter on a weekend retreat accidentally hit and kill a unicorn while en route to
find a billionaire's house, who seeks to exploit the creature's miraculous regenerative properties.
Death of a Unicorn had its world premiere at the South by Southwest Festival on March 8,
2025 and was released theatrically in North America by A24 on March 28, 2025.
It received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of dark comedy, blunt, macabre, unicorn, dark fantasy.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.